THOMAS TEMPLE

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

0422235683
tjt_84@hotmail.com
2703/315 La Trobe Street, Melbourne, 3000
<u>LinkedIn</u>
<u>GitHub</u>
Portfolio

ABOUT ME

I am a friendly, motivated individual who is looking for an entry into tech after completing the worlds #1 coding Bootcamp with Le Wagon. Originally from Scotland with Australian citizenship, I have been in Melbourne 3+ years and want to further solid my foundation in this great city. I am looking for a junior role with flexibility, culture and to be mentored by those with a high level of enthusiasm and experience.

TECH SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES2015, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails at Junior level.

Worked in an agile team environment using Slack, Trello, Git & GitHub. Used developer tools such as Figma for design, Cloudinary & several API.

CORE SKILLS

- Positive, people focused and well presented.
- Thrive on new challenges and responsibilities.
- Dependable timekeeping and time management qualities.
- Ability to work and collaborate in diverse, multi functioning team environment.
- Experience with teamwork and pair programming.
- Accurate with keen attention to detail with proficient typing skills.

INTERESTS

I take a deep interest in traveling, fitness, music festivals, and all things Scotland. As a passionate musician, I have been playing professionally for over ten years. I have also taught music privately for many years!

PROJECTS

<u>Lumina</u>

Team Project | Le Wagon Melbourne Rails with Ruby, Javascript, HTML & CSS, geocoding Mapbox features, AJAX, authorization & pundit gems...

SpinFinder

Team Project | Le Wagon Melbourne Includes multiple user pathways using a basic CRUD software architectural style. Built back to front collaboratively using an MVC software design pattern.

That's Rad Man

Personal Project
HTML/CSS & Design, Javascript, linear-gradient CSS
stylings, Bootstrap grid, Flexbox.

EXPERIENCE

Teacher Assistant

Le Wagon Melbourne | March 2021 - current Assisting with teaching HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES2015, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku, and Ruby on Rails.

Assistant Store Manager (2IC)

TOMS (Retail Prodigy Group) | Sept. 2018 - current Working closely with management, setting daily store budgets to help achieve sustainable sales growth. Coaching, development of staff, barista duties and operational tasks.

Internal Sales Representative

LOD Promotions & Workwear | April 2018 – July 2018 High level of administration, retail, B2B sales and customer service. Ordering and upkeep of stock levels from suppliers.

Business Control On Site (BCOS)

H&M - Hennes & Mauritz | Feb 2015 – August 2017 Managing and planning for 15+ teams. Worked with international departments to implement new global markets. Analysis of customer contacts/real-time workload management. Developed training material and ways of working.

EDUCATION

Le Wagon Melbourne

24-weeks Part Time Course Intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES2015, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.

Sussex University (Brighton Institute of Modern Music)

Professional Musicianship - August 2013 Learned the importance of SMART goals, research methods, and professional projects. Learning practical classes on performance, presentation style, and branding.